Milianopoulos, welcome to the show. And
you're not gay. I'm not gay. Nobody's
gay.
>> Peter Hitchens, welcome back to
Trigonometry. This I don't mean to give
a solution. It's not my job to give a
solution. I'm here to ring the alarm
bells on an issue that nobody's talking
about.
>> Tucker, what's going on with that laugh?
>> Oh, the laugh.
>> Douglas Murray, welcome back to
trigonometry.
>> Pleasure to be back with you. So,
Gary's economics.
>> So, I'm calling for a tax on the super
rich of anything above £10 million.
>> And what's what's your wealth?
>> 9,900,999.99.
>> Russell Brand, welcome to trigonometry.
How long have you been a Christian for?
And did it have anything to do with the
allegation?
>> Thomas Robinson,
there seems to be a lot of sniffing
going on here. People from Luton sniff
especially journalists from Luton. Who's
sniff?
>> Mileyopoulos, welcome to the show.
>> Pleasure to be here.
>> Um, so it's obviously been a traumatic
time. You've just been deported from
America.
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah. Pretty bad. Yeah.
>> Why were you deported?
>> Um, because it was a political witch
hunt. Um I because um um I hate women.
Um I think they don't like people who
are not gay. Um they they don't like
people who are completely heterosexual.
Um like me. Um and obviously um you know
you know that I'm um obviously not gay.
Um and I think that um Laura Luma, you
know, she just wants to be out. Um so
that's kind of um what it was. They just
um it's become so um so Trumpy uh so um
and
Laura Luma has is kind of in Trump's ear
and uh I just convinced him that um I
need to be out and um
>> they don't like they don't like people
who are not gay
>> and you're not gay.
>> I'm not gay. Nobody's gay.
>> Are you Are you married?
>> I'm I I I I'm married. Yeah. I'm a very
woman.
>> I I don't I I I don't actually like to
talk um um about
I'm married I'm married to a man, but I
don't do the um all the the sex stuff.
Um we don't do all that sex stuff um
anymore. Um my
>> So you're married to a man, but you
don't do the sex stuff, and therefore
you're not gay.
>> I'm not gay. You're straight.
>> Nobody's gay. There's no such thing.
Nobody's gay. There's no such thing as
gay. Um I actually live um he lives down
the corridor um in another state
completely. Um we live together, but the
down the corridor, other places. Um no,
I'm not gay. And you've you've tweeted
in the past that you kind of get
sexually aroused at the idea of people
being deported.
>> Yeah.
>> Why is that?
>> I just wanked off over it. I just wanked
off over um you know the idea that you
going behind a dumpster or or wherever
it is that I choose to actually go. Um I
just um behind wherever I can when I see
somebody being deported, especially
Somali, um I just um wank off.
Did you get aroused when you were
deported?
>> When 15 men um actually swarmed me and
and put me in handcuffs and I'm totally
not gay. Um I did get a little bit
aroused, but not because um of gay or
anything like that. It's not cuz I'm
gay.
Not gay.
Okay.
>> Milo, why don't you like women? Um I um
I kind of find them a little bit hard to
um uh actually relate to. I kind of hate
them probably because of my nebisha mom.
Um I hate my mom. Um and I you know I
see it as a flaw in myself. Um I see it
as a flaw. Um I have trouble uh
connecting to them. And um I just do
admit that maybe you got me, you know,
maybe you got me. I do uh kind of hate
women, but not cuz I'm gay. Um nothing
to do with being gay. Definitely. Okay.
>> What about feminism? Are you a fan of
feminism?
>> Um well, it makes everybody um
only attracts ugly women and fat women.
That's um most people are most most
girls are not actually um even they're
not feminists. They're not feminists.
Nobody's a feminist and nobody's gay.
>> Are you gay?
>> I'm not gay. Nobody is gay. You
>> used to go around saying you're gay.
I admit I used to say that kind of
thing. I used to say that a lot. I used
to admit I used to say that, you know, I
was married to a man. I I don't engage
in any of that sex stuff anymore.
>> Really? You used to talk about being
railed by your black husband, if I
remember correctly.
>> Yeah, I did. I used to say that kind of
thing.
>> So, when you were being railed by by
him, were you gay in that moment?
>> No. That was a trauma. That was a
trauma. That was the demon um that goes
into all gay gay men's heads that say,
"Just do it. Do it. Be be gay." and
they're not they're not actually gay. Um
they're not actually gay and it's
normally because they they just want to
um get some sort of um revenge um on
their nebisha mother. Um you know, so um
>> and uh you famously said you don't want
to move back to the UK because you don't
speak Arabic.
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah. Now that you've been forced to
move back to the UK, are you going to
start learning Arabic? Well, I I I don't
actually intend to be here much longer
than I um than than I'm going to fight
the case. Um but I did say it. I did say
that and I I I admit that I said it. Um
I don't know if I really meant it. A lot
of it is a joke. Um you know, I say
mean-spirited things all the time.
Totally not gay. Um but I say
meanspirited things all all the time.
And if you could call it a political
point, you can call it whatever you
want. Um but um I have to be careful
now. what I say now that I'm actually in
England could get lynched
>> indeed
>> by Somalis Somali people who they should
deport um completely they should
actually uh consider deporting all of
them in my opinion indiscriminately but
loosening the shackles.
>> Do you still support Donald Trump?
>> I've called him a traitor. Um I've
called him uh many things in the past.
I've never called for incitement the
same way people talk about this thing.
Apparently I was really bad to Laura
Loomer. I said crazy things about her.
I'm going to call it target practice. I
don't think that um u relates uh to um
incitement to violence. Calling for
target practice, does it? Is that is
that incitement? Would you say?
>> Yeah.
>> It's a pretty gay answer.
>> You're calling me gay?
>> That's a pretty gay answer. Yeah. But I
don't think you are.
>> So you're not gay?
>> No, because I thought there's no no
one's gay.
>> No, no one's gay. No one's gay except
Laura Loomer. She might be the only She
might uh be the only uh genuine lesbian.
Um I think she's actually a man. Um she
wishes she was me. She hates herself so
much. Um
>> and uh what are you looking forward to?
Are you look are you going to try and
get back to America?
>> I'm going to fight this. Yeah. And
hopefully um with a little bit of luck,
I might be arrested by 15 or 20 of these
men again. Um uh at the border, not
because I'm okay. Um just because I want
to apologize to all of them. And a lot
of people in ICE lost their jobs
actually because um uh they didn't want
to do this. They didn't want to do it.
>> They lost their jobs.
>> They lost their jobs. Some of them said
I think oh we don't want to do this.
>> This isn't what we signed up for. And um
one of them was really strapping
actually. In fact they all were. All of
them were really strapping handsome men
on the gateway
obviously.
>> And Milo, what's the one thing we're not
talking about that we really should be
>> deporting Somalis? they should be
deported um indiscriminately. The the
the um immigration system needs to work
and it's not doing that. It's not
working the way it should be.
>> It seems to be in America.
>> No, it's not for people like me. It's
for people like Somali.
>> Yeah,
>> makes sense. Thanks for coming on, Ma.
>> Yeah, my pleasure. By the way,
>> Peter Hitchens, welcome back to
Trigonometry. How are you?
So far so good.
>> Yes, indeed. And what do you make of the
state of Britain at the moment?
>> Well, I mean, it's finished. It's
totally finished country. I I I never
seen a country more finished. I mean,
what's what have we got to show for us
at the moment? You have a police force
that may as well have been abducted by
aliens about as effective as as a
chocolate fire guard. We have What else
do we have? We have a criminal justice
system that may as well have been
written by Stalin's pre-revolutionary
bandits and expropriators. And just as
you think,
it couldn't get any worse. You have
Andrew Burnham becoming prime minister
and and and and and mounting an assault
on the last vestigages of of of
everything that we we can that we may
have pride in the language. I mean, who
calls a bap a starty or a cob or
whatever else he calls it? If he knew
anything about British Baps, I doubt
he's ever read around the subject at
all. And if he has, he's obviously done
so with the lights off.
It's ludicrous calling British Baps a
Scotty or a cop or a bomb. It's was my
never seen a country more finished.
Although I will say I will say that she
has inspired me to write my next book.
It's called the betrayal of the British
paps, how Andrew Burnham burnt the
British bakery revolution.
>> And um you've you're famously outspoken
about the the terrible effects of weed.
Would you say it's marijuana is the
worst drug?
>> Well, there there are many things that
are arguably worse than this. I mean the
the constant clock fiddling every single
year moving it forward by an hour is is
is ludicrous and disgraceful. Although
yes, I have I have answered this
question many times. If you think that
I'm going to stay here now talking to
both of you for an hour to discuss
drugs. I've already said and I'm
starting to wonder whether actually both
of you are obsessed with drugs. Are you
on drugs yourselves? Perhaps you are.
You would know that I've already spoken
about this.
>> And have you ever tried marijuana
yourself?
is is if you ask me another question
about drugs, I will storm out this. This
this doesn't flow. You've invited me
here into false pretenses. I would never
try marijuana. Marijuana. I would never
try it. It's it's it's one of the worst
things that have happened to society. I
smell it. I can hear the people giggling
away as it's like little pet children. I
don't want any part of it. And it is it
is responsible for the downfall and the
abolition of Britain. I've been talking
about this for years. Nobody's bothered
to listen, but it's rather amusing to
watch.
>> And uh geopolitical question now. Would
you say that Russia was provoked into
invading Ukraine?
>> Well, what individual with a prefrontal
cortex thinks otherwise was I' I've
tried my best to convince people and get
into their heads and explain to them
that Russia did not need to be provoked.
It didn't need to be provoked. What was
what was it? I if I could, I'd get into
people's heads and I'd seduce them with
facts, but people don't want to be
seduced and I don't have the powers of
seduction. And I never have. And I've
I've said now for decades I've said,
why would Russia ever agree to NATO
expansion? Why would he ever agree to
that? There's no reason for it. Many
have tried to invade Russia over the
years, over over the centuries and
decades. The Swedish and French tries in
the 1700s. Napoleon tried it in the
1800s. Hitler tried it with Operation
Barbar Russ in 1941. Why would they
accept this? They didn't need to be
provoked.
And Peter, how does it feel to be
correct about everything?
>> Well, I say no pleasure in this. I'm
pleased as everybody gets eventually
people have realized that now I'm now
told I'm always writing the obituary for
for Great Britain. I am rights all the
time. Nobody build a solution. If they
did, they could have stopped it. But it
is rather amusing to watch, I suppose. I
don't take any pleasure in it. I never
used to. But I can't influence it. I
can't influence. I can't make people do
the things that are necessary to
reverse. The revolution's already
happened. There are cars everywhere. Why
do we see so many cars? I was right
about the cars as well. It's ludicrous.
>> And what is your advice for young people
now growing up in this country? a will I
don't know I don't know how to advise
them what can I possib What advice can I
give I mean there is no sunshine and
rainbows there is no happiness in this
world it's all gray and miserable the
sooner they accept that the better it
becomes the easier life is I I really
don't know perhaps for a start I'd say
master the art of voting don't vote for
what you do wants you won't get it
you'll only be disappointed vote for
vote against what you don't want and you
might be able to stop it. Other than
that, what can I say? Pack a bag and go
and find a a monastery high up in a
mountain somewhere and live in a
shangria. Other than that, I don't know.
>> So, here's the most important question
we've ever asked on trigonometry. Shag,
marry, kill, Tony Blair, Boris Johnson,
Zack Palanski.
>> I assume you mean Anthony Blair and
Zachary.
>> Well, I I'll start with Boris Johnson.
I'll start with him. I wouldn't shag
him. You can't shag him because he's a
plastic conservative. There's nothing
real about him. Although he has proven
himself to be quite unsuccessful in the
union of marriage. So at least I'd have
the sweet liberator of divorce for so
I'd marry him. Although I am fairly sure
that if I was to marry him I'd probably
unknowingly be engaged in some sort of
scheme of bigamy. I don't know.
Regarding Anthony Blair,
he's he's one of the worst prime
ministers, possibly the worst prime
ministers that we've ever had in this
country and and and he's responsible for
some of the worst things that this have
led to the decline of of Great Britain.
So, and but he has also shown himself at
the same time, he shown himself to be
rather adept in the union of marriage.
So, I wouldn't have the sweet liberator
of divorce to look forward to. So, I
suppose I'd have to I I don't want to
use the word Shaq again. So, I suppose
I'd have to punish and pound him for his
sins. Let's leave it at that.
>> And Zach Palansky.
>> Zachary Palansky. Yes. Well, I knew this
was going to be a process of of
elimination. Zack Zachary Pollinsky is
is somebody who who I suppose that
leaves me with no choice, but I' I'd
rather not use the the F-word or the
sword again. I'm going to have to
substitute. I don't believe in killing
anybody. So, I'm going to have to
substitute the kword for fm.
>> So, you shag them all.
>> Shag them all. Yes.
>> Would you take any pleasure in
>> No, I'd mar I'd marry Boris Johnson. You
don't listen. This is your You don't
listen. Open your ears and learn
something. I said I'd marry Boris
Johnson because of the sweet liberation
of divorce. I said I'd shag or I said
I'd pound and punish Anthony Blair for
his sins. and I said I'd f Zachary
Palansky. You don't have to like my
answer, but you have to listen to it.
You don't have to agree with this. I
don't care. I'm in the twilight of my
life. It makes no difference to me.
>> And Peter, final question. What's the
one thing we're not talking about that
we should be?
>> Cars. We're not talking about
appliances. We're not talking about mass
ownership. We don't need cars anymore.
We need to abolish the cars. And not
only that, we need to abolish kettles.
The amount of electricity that the
kettle uses is ludicrous. Totally
unacceptable. Same goes for washing
machines.
>> Hold on. Hold on, Peter. Hold on a
second. A cup of tea is the most British
thing ever. You want to abolish kettle?
>> I I have no problem with a cup of tea.
It's the kettles. It's the kettles.
People boil them again and again and
again and again. And they're destroying
the climate with all the electricity
consumption. Same goes the same goes for
the washing machines. Putting them on
the cycles for hours. They go round and
round and round for hours and hours and
hours and nobody bothers to talk about
it. This is going to lead to the
complete destruction of of Britain. If
you think it's not, it's quite amusing
to watch both of you. You naive littles.
>> Wait, how would you wash clothes without
washing machines?
>> Well, you I don't need to give a
solution. It's not my job to give a
solution. I'm here to ring the alarm
bells on on an issue that nobody's
talking about. The principles that
nobody wants to talk about.
I'm I'm done giving solutions. I don't
need to.
Would be a complete waste of my time.
Running a business for as long as I
have, you start to notice a pattern. The
businesses that lose the most money
aren't necessarily the ones with a bad
product. They're the ones where the
phone rang or a message came in and
nobody was there to answer it in time.
Today's episode is brought to you by
Quo, spelled Quo, the business phone
system built so you never miss a call.
What Quo actually does is
straightforward. Every call, text, and
voicemail lands in one place so whoever
on your team looks at it can see the
full exchange and pick it up from there
instead of starting cold. Several years
into running the show, you learned that
most operational problems aren't solved
by hiring more people. that solved by
better systems. That is why Quo stands
out. It's simple enough to set up in
minutes and doesn't require anyone on
the team to become an IT person
overnight. And when nobody on your team
is free to pick up, an AI agent takes
the call, answers the office questions,
and can book someone in immediately. The
lead doesn't sit overnight going cold,
which is usually when you lose the
business. Money is always on the line.
Always say hello with Quo. Try Quo for
free, plus get 20% off for your first 6
months when you go to quo.com/trig.
That's quo.com/trig.
Tucker Carson, this has been a long time
coming. Thanks for coming on the show.
Uh, why is everything Israel's fault?
>> Well, I don't think there's any doubt
that everything is Israel's fault.
everything like
>> but look I mean I think it's really
clear and we know that because I've
spoken to preeminent historians of
everything actually and it is
>> like a
>> well like Daryl Cooper you have a
problem with him
>> he's one of the most pre-minent
historians ever he's not a pseudo
historian he's real is he
>> it's not revisionist he's real right and
so I know that everything is Israel's
fault even though I don't ever think
I've actually said that even now I don't
think those words have even left my lips
I don't think I've ever said that,
right? And so, I mean, even this coffee
is actually kind of cold. Israel. I
tried to tie my shoelaces this morning
and I realized it was quite difficult.
And guess what? Blue and white shoes.
>> Yeah.
>> Was that Israel? That is Israel. That is
Israel. That's just a fact. And I'm not
going to apologize for that either, by
the way. And it's not only everyday life
that it's Israel. It's also It's not
even only in politics. It's everything
that I do. I just see Israel everywhere.
And I just see it. I'm like like I took
my dogs for a walk walk the other day
and one of them suddenly got sick and I
said, "Oh my god, are you okay?" And I
looked down and she said, "Woof." And I
got closer. I said, "Is everything
okay?" And suddenly I hear saying,
"Israel did this to me. Israel did this
to me. I really want you to think about
that as Christians actually." And it's
unbelievable, right?
>> Yeah. It is kind of hard to believe.
>> Well, I'm not going to apologize for it.
It's just a fact. It's just a fact. And
it's out there on the internet. I'm not
making this up. I also heard actually I
love going for walks as I say with my
dogs my wife my bless my wife I love my
wife I really do what I do without her
and I heard these this kind of
twittering from a bird it sound like a
beeper and it turns out actually that it
exploded because Israel had planted a
pager an explosive pager in one of the
birds and exploded because they thought
it was his bullah hisbola
and no actually it was um it was Israel
so Israel is actually killing the birds
and making my dogs sick.
>> Israel is making your dog sick. Speaking
of of of dogs and things being sick, uh
have you been scratched by any more
demons lately? Because I know it's a
it's a big thing.
>> Well, this is just another thing that
people laugh at, and I know you don't
believe it, but it's true. It happens
just to be a fact actually. And if you
don't believe me, ask Darl Cooper. So, I
woke up. I've told the story a few
times, but I don't mind telling you
again. And what the actual what the
coincidence of it is. So, I woke up and
I found that I'd had I went to bed
obviously with four hunting dogs and
bears and tigers and I woke up with
scratches and I my wife looked at me and
she said, "Oh my god, I think you've
been scratched by a demon." I said,
"Really? What?" Turns out it's really
normal actually and happens all the
time. And I lifted my arm up and my
wife's my wife noticed that I had
scratch marks here and she said, "I
think we should count them." And there
were 74 of them. And at the time, do you
know how old Israel was? 74. We also
count on the second side and there were
two giant scratch marks that were the
exact shape of Ben Shapiro's eyebrows.
So it was Ben Shapiro in Israel.
Obviously, I think
>> Ben Shapiro scratched you during the
night.
>> Well, I don't think I think the evidence
is just out there. You can look that up.
I don't have to convince you of
anything. Actually,
>> well, I'm not you. You've repeatedly
said you you want to apologize, but no
one's asked you.
>> I'm not going to apologize for anything.
I'm not going to apologize for anything
ever. But don't even know what an
apology means. What even is an apology?
Do you even know what that means?
>> Yeah, I do.
>> What's an apology?
>> It's when you say sorry.
>> I think we have to define what we mean
by apologize.
>> I'm defining it. It's when you say
sorry.
>> Well, no, actually it's No, it's not
actually when you say sorry. It's when
you actually regret regret what you're
saying and you mean it.
>> Oh, so you do know what an apology is.
>> Well, no, I don't know. I don't even
know what you just asked. Are we even
here now? I'm here.
>> No, I'm not going to apologize for
anything.
>> All right. Can I ask you another
question?
>> Well, of course, when you open free
speech and dialogue, right, you can ask
questions. We love asking questions,
right?
>> Yeah, I thought so. Um, what's your
favorite thing about Qatar?
>> Well, Qar for me represents the American
dream. Actually,
it is a place where, and I know
everybody's going to hear that, they're
going to say Qatar.
Yeah, I do love Qar and I recently
bought a property there actually. I
don't know if you heard about it. It's a
beautiful place, beautiful culture, and
as a proud, ashamed American, I go there
all the time.
>> And I'm not ashamed to say that because
that's my way of saying [__] you. I'm
allowed to do it as an American. I have
more in common with Qataris than I do
most Americans. And I'm proud to say
that as a proud ashamed American, just
like when I come to England, actually, I
have more in common with a Pakistani
driver than I do with any of the English
people. And I'm allowed to say that
because I'm British.
>> What What do you have in common with a
Pakistani driver?
>> Just everything. way we everything the
way we dress the way we think the way we
go both go to QARQAR
and that's really it I don't think I
really need to say also the Christian
thing I have a lot in common with
Pakistani cab drivers over the
>> yeah there's a lot of overlap Sharia law
are you a fan
>> I think Sharia law was better better
than only fans better than pornography
I'd rather have Sharia law than forcing
all women oh my god we want the only
fans
No, we don't want that. I would rather
way rather go and live in Qatar under
Sharia law or have it here. And I don't
think there's anything wrong with that.
And by the way, Daryl Cooper agrees with
me on that.
>> Do are Israel controlling everyone and
everything? Tucker,
>> I really don't think there's any doubt
about that. Actually, I think it's
really clear if you look at everything.
And by the way, I don't even know if
it's true. I just like to ask questions.
And I think that Donald Trump is a real
slave to Israel. I think that's clear,
right? I don't think there's any doubt
about that anymore. I don't think he
takes any I don't think he makes any
decisions that are not controlled by
Israel. I mean, he went went to attack
Maduro. Maduro. What else gets Maduro?
And the way that he supports Ukraine and
doesn't like Putin apparently. I mean,
he says he gets on with him, but he
continues to back Ukraine. And I know a
lot of people hear that and they'll
they'll just think that I'm saying I
love Putin. Putin. Putin.
>> I don't love Putin. Actually, I don't
love Maduro. I love Qar more than I do
America. But I do think that Israel is
basically responsible for all of it. And
I just don't think there's any doubt
about that.
>> So, uh, are we being controlled by
Israel?
>> Well, who paid you to ask that question?
I think that's the real thing. And also,
what color shirt is that? And what color
skin are you?
>> It's an Israeli shirt.
>> It is. It's Yeah,
>> right. And what color skin are you? I'm
just asking questions.
>> It's pretty pale.
>> Yeah, it's very similar to the Israeli
flag.
>> Are you scared that if you say white,
I'm a racist.
>> What color of skin are you? White.
White. Right.
>> Yes.
>> You're wearing the colors of the Israeli
flag. You're totally controlled. You
probably took 7K even to ask me that.
Right.
I don't know what to say about you
actually. But you're probably controlled
by He probably controls you. Israel
controls him. And that's how it works. I
I I know that because I've actually been
there. I've been in Washington. And I've
seen how this works. It is a drip kind
of control where the people at the top
control and they're controlling him and
he's controlling you actually. So yeah,
you are controlled by Israel. I don't
think there's any doubt about that.
>> This is a question I really wanted to
ask. Do you But do you think moving on
that Churchill is the greatest villain
of World War II?
>> Well, I think that there's no doubt
about that either. You're asking me
questions where there is actually no
doubt Churchill was the chief villain. I
mean, he bombed the Nazis. I know people
are going to hear that and say Nazi
Nazi. No, he is the chief villain of
World War II. He did not have to bomb
the Nazis. I don't believe in bombing
anybody. I don't believe in killing
anybody. Includes Germans. Includes
Nazis. Actually, not a Nazi.
And also, you have to remember as well
that he was the one that dragged
Roosevelt into the war. He dragged him
in. Right? I don't think you know about
that because you've probably never
spoken to the pre-minent historian of
World War II. I have a lot of times
actually. I've read his books.
>> And that was against his will. Roosevelt
didn't want to get involved in a war.
What? To kill Nazis or overtaking the
continent of Europe? Like people were
really scared of that? Really? You think
that people really cared about that? No.
He was a chief villain and there was no
need for that. But it wasn't just
Churchill. You have to remember also
that it was actually David Beng.
He actually convinced Churchill to drag
Roosevelt into the war. So it was Israel
as well. Actually,
>> wait. Israel was created in 1948.
>> Well, that doesn't matter.
>> Doesn't matter, does it?
>> Doesn't it?
>> I'm asking questions. We'll have to ask
questions. And Benurion existed before
1948. He actually wanted the war to go
on so that he could get more sympathy
and then establish the state of Israel
so he could control the United States of
America, which would then control
Francis, which would then control you
and your entire podcast. And it's not
even a conspiracy to say that actually.
And you have to remember as well, David
Bengone, he under he undermined DA. He
was undermining it. Yeah. And he he
caused Pearl Harbor. Who do you think
got the Japanese to bomb? You think it
was just the Japanese? The bad Japanese?
>> No, it wasn't. Of course not.
>> It was Israel.
>> Well, it was David Beng.
Of course, it's just a fact. It's out
there. Not making it up.
>> Definitely not.
>> Definitely not making it up. You can
check that up on the internet. I mean
that.
Well, some people have said that your
obsession with Israel is more about
Jews.
>> Oh, it's not the Jews. I know a lot of
people say that because they WANT TO
SAY, "SHUT UP. Shut up, Nazi."
No, it's nothing to do with Jews. I
don't have a problem with the Jews. Have
a problem with a stupid country that is
claiming to be Jewish. Had nothing to do
with Judaism, actually. Just a fact. And
nobody disputes that at all. You just
quoting lines now from BB Netanyahu like
your boss.
Who's your boss? He is your boss, isn't
he? Why don't you just come out and
admit it? You know how I know that?
Candace told me. I put more currency in
Candace Owen's podcast than anything
that you've ever said. If she tells me
that you're controlled by Israel, I
believe her. You know why? Feelings. She
has a feeling. And I don't doubt that.
>> So, the what's the one thing we're not
talking about that we should be?
I hate to say it. Israel. I hate to say
it. We're not talking about it. I don't
want to talk about Israel. People are
like, "Oh, YOU'RE AN ANTI-SEMITE. SHUT
UP." I don't want to talk about Israel.
I don't care about stupid Israel. I
don't want to talk about Ben Shapiro
either, actually. So, Israel,
>> what are your thoughts on Ben Shapiro?
>> I feel sorry for him. I really do. I
really feel sorry for him. I think that
Ben Shapiro is one of the worst
podcasters ever. He's been blown up,
juiced his numbers, made out like he's
kind of talented, has opinions, none of
them are really his own. And he's a
slave. And actually, he's he's not even
a slave. Actually, he's the master of
slaves. He controls everybody. You can't
get a mortgage because of Ben Shapiro.
Your Taco Bells, the price of your Taco
Bell is actually going up because of Ben
Shapiro. And he says, "Shut up. Shut up.
Eat your Taco Bell." It's all Ben
Shapiro. You have to live outside of New
York City where your grandfathers and
your grandparents grew up. What? That's
Ben Shapiro says, "Get out. Can't afford
it, peasant." What is that? He's
literally the worst. He's worse than
anything under my shoe. And I mean that.
He's actually worse than Mark Lein. I
didn't think that was possible.
>> Tucker, what's going on with that laugh?
>> Oh, the laugh.
>> Yeah, substances will do that. Actually,
a lot of substances will do that when
you consume a lot of alcohol and other
kinds of things. But the truth is, I
never really talk about this and I will
now. Basically, when I believe something
and I've said something so outrageous, I
just laugh it off as if you never really
heard me say it, as if I didn't mean it.
So, when somebody says like, "You're an
anti-semite."
I'm not an anti-semite. Never have been.
Don't believe in that. don't believe in
blood guilt at all. Like at all and I
don't love Maduro. Maduro. I don't love
Putin. Putin. I know you love Putin. I
know maybe you love Putin. I don't love
Putin. I don't care what anybody says.
And so when I say that I don't love
Putin. And I go
kind of means I do actually. Kind of
means I do.
That's right. Same as when people say,
"Shut up, Nazi. You're an anti-semite.
You're a Nazi." No, I'm not a Nazi at
all.
And I don't love Nick Fuentes.
>> Patrick Bed David, welcome back to
trigonometry.
>> My pleasure to be here. Right.
>> So, what did you think?
>> Wait, wait. Did you just call me Rod?
>> I said right. Right.
>> Oh, right.
>> Right. K. That's what I said. I say K.
Right. You want to say it? Right.
>> Right. Right.
>> Right.
>> Yeah.
>> You can proceed with the question that
you want to ask. Right.
>> Okay.
>> So, uh, Patrick, what did you make of
Kansas's debate with Andrew Wilson?
>> So, do you want to know what I thought?
I I I know that a lot of people were
complaining about that. Right. A lot of
people were complaining. They were
saying that, you know, you took too much
money or they took too much money. I
want to tell you something. I don't know
if you're ready for this, but here's
where I'm going with this. I don't know
if you're ready for this. Are you ready
for this?
>> Right.
>> Absolutely.
>> Right. Say right.
>> Right.
>> Right. Right.
>> Right. Got it. So I actually think that
the bape was one of the most important
things that has happened in this decade.
And the reason for that is because is
because everybody got to see what are
the facts. They heard facts from
Candace. They heard facts from Andrew
Wilson. I respect both of them. And the
most important things that everybody was
baptized. Baptizing is key, right?
Candace, she was able to baptize
everybody with her part of the argument.
And guess what? Andrew was able to do
the same. I thought it was I thought it
was insightful. I think it was the most
important debate and I don't think
there's anything even close to that and
I was just talking to Adam about this
and he agreed. I was actually just
sitting uh for dinner with one of my
millionaire friends the other day and he
even said, "You know who really wins
from all of this? The markets guy."
>> And how much were you paid for the
debate?
>> So, here's the thing. You ready for
this? I wasn't paid anything. And they
said to me, "Do you want $1 million, $2
million, $3 million?" They said I said,
"You know what? I don't want a thing.
All I want is to be able to to advertise
what's most important because I'm doing
this for Charlie Kirk. I'm doing this
for the markets. I'm doing this for the
people at home. And I said that all I
wanted was for her to get $300,000. And
I wanted I wanted uh uh uh Andrew Wilson
to get subscribers. That was uh to
remember Charlie, how Charlie would want
to be remembered, obviously. And uh I
wanted to advertise a shoe that blends
comfort,
>> function,
>> and luxury. a shoe. The future looks
bright. Shoe bride looks bright.
>> And um do you think you did a good job?
You know what I think? And I was
discussing this also with Vinnie before.
I think that no other moderator would
have done what I did. Right. Because I
don't think if anybody else had debated
that there would have been more ads,
right? I don't think that there would
have been a lot more ads. I don't think
uh the people were interested in seeing
anything except the ads that I was
showing which were for the future of his
bride shoe. Uh they could have been made
fast and could have been made cheap. I
chose neither. So I went to Tuscan,
Italy to make my future bride shoe ride
and uh I think I did a fantastic job.
>> Okay.
>> Okay. Would you say Candace is the best
debater in the world?
>> I would say that Candace is very
talented. She came calm. She came
collected. I respected what she said. I
respected that she brought her facts and
she backed it up with evidence such as
her dreams and feelings and vibes. I
respected that. And also, I think that a
lot of people don't talk about this when
it comes to Candace Owens. Uh she
actually is one of the most talented
negotiators. And I know that because I'm
a businessman, you know, I'm worth
hundreds of millions of dollars. Uh uh
one 100 million, two million, 300
million dollars. Uh but I didn't want
the money. I didn't want anything for
it. But she's one of the most fantastic
negotiators because uh I'll tell you
this and I've never revealed this to
anybody. Are you ready for this? So when
she said, "I want to do this for Charlie
because my priority and her priority is
Charlie and the memory of Charlie Kirk."
She wanted to start, she said she wanted
to start at $2 million from Andrew
Wilson, right?
And I realized after she settled for
$300,000
to remember Charlie, right? That's what
she did. And she knew from the beginning
that we were going to settle at
$300,000. So she started so high. She
went up a little bit, then she went up a
little bit, up a bit, then she went down
a little bit, then she went up a little
bit, then she came down and she settled.
And you know what? I think that the real
winner in all of this is it's Erica
Kirk. Erica Kirk has now got to see the
facts. They debated it. They had it out.
I respect that. And so, I think she's a
very talented person. Uh, and I'm I'm
pleased for her for $300 that she made
out of this guy.
>> So, you all did this for Charlie.
>> The entire thing was for Charlie. I
didn't want a penny for it. I just
wanted to advertise. I just thought that
it was important for the world to see a
shoe that that combines comfort,
function, and luxury. A shoe that could
have been made anywhere else. It could
have been made fast and cheap. I chose
Naider. You know about that. If you want
to buy any from me after this, the
future is bright. We can do this. I
thought that was the most important
thing. And you know what? I made
hundreds of millions of dollars. You
know why I did that? You ready for this?
I did it for Charlie.
Patrick, thank you for coming back on
the show. What's the one thing we're not
talking about that we really should be?
>> I think we're not talking about the
markets enough. I think we should be
talking about how the markets are going
up a little bit and going down a little
bit. I think a lot of people also are
not talking about how they don't hear me
out. People need to hear me out. They
need to wait in suspense and hear my
point, right?
That's it. The trigonometry merch store
is built on Shopify because the moment
someone's actually ready to pay, Shopify
makes sure they can. And if they've
bought before, their details are already
saved. So, it's one tap and done. That's
time back to grow the business instead
of running it. If you want to start the
same way, that's shopify.co.uk/trigger.
With Shopify, nothing stands between
your idea and a real business. So, go
make it one. Start your free trial at
shopify.co.uk/trigger.
Start your free trial at
>> Douglas Murray, welcome back to
Trigonometry.
>> Pleasure to be back with you.
>> So,
how do you uh reflect back on your
debate with Dave Smith?
>> Uh, well, I mean, first of all, I think
they should insist at the outset of
calling him by his real name, comic Dave
Smith.
Um, I mean, what does he know about
anything? That was a long, long time
ago.
Uh, he should not be platformed for
anything except on how to be an expert
on being a comedian, never actually
writing anything funny.
Uh, I mean, has he ever been to any of
these places he's he ever opines about?
I don't think he has.
>> Have you been?
>> Well, of course I've been, but he's
never been anywhere. We'll get to where
I've been in a moment.
Uh but comedies, as far as I can tell,
he's only ever been to America.
He's never been to Israel. He's never
been to the Gaza. What does he know
about Hamas?
Doesn't know anything about I mean his
level of intellect is so low uh that he
would literally make dumb and dumber
even dumber if they had to listen to
him.
>> So coming back to have you been have you
been? Well, of course I've been I've
been to a lot of it. I don't like to
talk about anywhere even in passing
unless I've at least been there. Have
you ever been? That's the question. Have
you ever been Have you been to any of
the places about which you opine? I
don't think so. I've been to Israel.
I've dined with Prime Minister
Netanyahu.
I've been to the IDF headquarters in Tel
Aviv. I've sat in the chair of Yaha
Sinoir. I've been to these places.
I don't think anybody should be talking
about anything unless they've at least
been there. No. No.
>> So, Douglas, this is a question I've
wanted to ask you for the for for the
longest time. Who is your favorite
member of the LGBTQIA+
community?
>> I suppose it's rather like asking which
of of Comedy Dave Smith's jokes are the
worst. because there's so many to choose
from.
Uh I mean, if I really had to choose
which is the worst [__] of that little
so-called community, I mean, it would
have to be Owen Jones, wouldn't it? Uh
it's too bad that there isn't an F in
LGBTQ of a freak, which he would of
course exclusively occupy.
I mean, he's just another one of these
people whose rationale is so
unfathomable to me. I mean, he seems to
be hellbent on positioning himself as
the architect of importing the
equivalent of Chop Chop Square into
London, of which he, of course, would be
the the first victim for obvious
reasons. He's like a little hair
attempting to ingratiate himself with
the wolf. His thought process is
unfathomable to me, and he's totally
repellent. Totally repellent.
Uh, well, on that very subject, how much
would we have to pay here at Trig to get
you to go on a date with Owen?
>> We'll crowdfund it.
>> Yeah.
>> Oh, I mean, it's a very strange kind of
question that, isn't it? I mean,
>> I suppose very strange line of
questioning. I suppose it's kind of like
me asking you respectively uh who would
you rather go would how much would I
have to pay you to go on a date with in
your case Leon Brev or your case
Nicholas Madura although I suppose and
have a sneaky suspicion that you would
like to meet with Nicholas Madur in some
capacity if only to remind him that you
two are Venezuelan.
Uh but no truthfully I mean no amount of
money could get me. I mean what would
that date even look like? I can see it
now. Picture it now for 2 hours sitting
across a dinner table from Owen Jones,
the reprehensible Owen Jones as he
herangs me on why the tablecloths are
racist for being white. Uh, no, I
wouldn't do that. I mean, I don't know
what the amount is exactly, but I will
say this, and this is very difficult to
admit publicly. I think rather than go
on a date uh with Owen Jones, I'd
probably rather sit through an entire
set of comic Dave Smith or be lectured
to on the art of sanity by Candice
Owens. All of which are enough to make
one want to wrap a 50 kg weight around
your head and dive into the deepest part
of the Pacific head first. I can see it
now. The headlines would be the strange
death of Douglas Murray.
Gary's economics. It's been a long time
coming, but welcome to the show. So,
firstly, why are you quitting public
life?
>> Cuz I'm tired. I'm tired. Listen, I'm
I'm going to be honest, right? When you
have come from being the most
unprofitable peasant in Milford to being
the most profitable trader in City Bank,
it is tiring. I cannot carry this cross
alone. The peasants have got to do it.
The peasants have got to get the poor
people at home like you have got to get
your act together and tax the rich. I'm
tired. I'm quitting.
>> So why are you back? Why are you doing
this interview?
>> Cuz I got tired of quitting. I got tired
of quitting. Listen, if I don't come
back into the podcast space and my my
campaigning, listen, I don't need to do
this, right? I could be like playing
crusade crusader king sue, you know,
traveling [__] Japan. I don't need to
be here. Where, by the way, I learn a
lot of my history and economics from
Crusader King Sue. But I I'm coming back
to save the peasants at home. I'm a bit
like Robin Robin Hood, right? I am the
one that speaks speaks truth to power
and cause for taxing the super rich.
We've got to tax super rich. Otherwise,
I'm just going to get tired again.
>> How often do you get tired? I just get
tired all the time. If I listen, first
it started with Gary's economics, which
now we should name this to trigonomics
or whatever. But I got tired of
quitting. Quitomics is tiring when you
have learned everything that there is to
know in economics, right? And you are
City Bank's most profitable trader and
also you are you've got a degree from
LSC and Oxford. Listen, I'm going to be
honest. It's all time. I don't need to
be here. here. I don't even want to be
here.
>> So,
>> I'm doing it for you.
>> Thank you, Gary. I appreciate that. So,
if wealth taxes don't work, should we
still implement them? What is the
alternative? Listen, what is the
alternative? If you don't start taxing
the super rich now, right? Listen, how
many how much passive passive income do
you make? I know this question. How much
passive income do you make? Just being
here, it's hundreds of thousands of
pounds, right? You have got to be taxed.
You have got to be taxed.
>> We don't make any passive income. What
are you talking about?
>> You make passive income just from when
you are sitting there on your YouTube
channel. I know how it works.
>> Right. You are not doing anything. That
is passive.
>> So you're saying you make hundreds of
thousands of pounds in passive income.
>> I'm saying that you listen I'm going to
be honest. I I do not want to just tax
the rich because I hate the rich. I know
the problem with the rich. I own a lot
of [__] assets, right?
How many how how wealthy are you?
>> So I'm calling for a tax on the super
rich of anything above £10 million. £10
million
>> and what's what's your wealth?
>> 9,900,999.99.
So listen, I'm part part of the pat
millionaires. I if I could I would pay
Listen, I want to get taxed. I want to
get [__] government don't tax me.
>> Really? You know, there's a there's a
website the government has where you can
go and pay tax voluntarily if you feel
strongly about needing to pay more tax.
>> I'm tired. Too tired for that. I don't
listen, it's not like I'm going to I
could be anywhere that I want. It's not
like I'm going to start going out trying
to sign up saying tax me tax me. No.
What the government needs is a system in
place to just get taxing people like me
making millions of pounds. It is hard
making millions of pounds.
>> I don't want to make millions of pounds.
I don't want it.
>> So,
>> I'm doing it for you.
>> You're doing it for me.
>> Doing it for both of you.
>> And the peasants at home.
>> And and the peasants and and the
peasants at home. So, you're worth
£9,999,999.99.
>> Precisely. Yeah.
>> And what is the threshold that you want
to bring in?
>> £10 million.
>> Why is that, Gary?
>> That's the fair way to do it. Listen,
there's nothing that is that is the
difference between Listen, you two laugh
at it, but that is the difference
between super rich and rich.
>> I don't know how much you're you're
worth. I would estimate about 20 million
pounds. You should be paying 2% of that.
Otherwise, listen, the rich are going to
get rich, the poor are going to get
poorer. It is very simple. And then the
consequences, I'm going to own
everything. I don't want to own
everything. I'm tired of it.
So Gary, this is a question I've always
wanted to ask you, mate. Why do you
dress like you're homeless?
>> Well, listen. When I when I wrote my
book, which you should buy not to make
me any more millions of pounds. I don't
want it.
I called my sister up, right? And she
was like, "Listen, you got to be a
[__] to appeal to the peasants, the
poor people, the scum. You've got to be
you've got to be a dickhead." So I
actually own all the clothes at home,
right? I if you go into the high street
now the reality is you will not find any
clothes cuz I [__] own all of them.
Iing own all of them and but I don't
have to wear them. I own all of the
clothes and assets you will get from the
high street. You will not find any cuz
cuz I'm so rich I can just buy
everything. But I want to remind all the
I suppose it is my job to just act like
a peasant. So I dress like a homeless
person,
>> look like a [__] sound like a
[__]
and despite that, still be City Bank's
most profitable trader with a degree
from MC in Oxford.
>> Oh, Gary, one of the things I found
interesting is, right, you're quitting
because you're tired because the work is
too much. Why is one YouTube video a
week too much work?
>> Listen, I'm going to be honest, right?
When I was at Oxford, I was doing one
essay a week. One essay a week on
economics, but the poor are getting
poorer, the rich are getting richer. And
I decided I didn't want to give it to
the professors anymore because they
honestly they didn't know I had some
artwork. The professors at Oxford knew
all about economics and tax inequality.
So I remember I would see like these I'd
see all these like professors and these
little Oxford wankers, right? Wearing a
little cape. So I decided I was going to
make a YouTube channel. I made a YouTube
channel. Obviously was getting 20,000,
you know, new subscribers a day, making
millions of pounds. People subscribed to
the Patreon where I make millions of
pounds. Don't want those millions of
pounds. And honestly, it just became the
Gary Stevenson show. I I didn't want it
anymore. You know, you know what I mean?
I don't need to do this. I can just go
to [__] Japan, play Crusader King
Sue. It just became too much. So I quit.
>> Did you enjoy your time at Oxford?
>> That was full of just Oxford wankers who
don't understand economics. I, you know,
I just rock up every everywhere in
Oxford, right? They make you wear that
little Oxford wank wanker cape. I just
go in my AC and my little hoodie, my
beanie hat or whatever. And they charge
me 30 [__] grand. I want mying money
back. Not that I need it.
So Gary, uh, what's the one thing we're
not talking about that we really should
be?
>> How tired I am. It is a real thing.
Being tired is something that people
talk about mental health. People talk
about tax inequality. I am talking about
that. I can't do it alone. I'm like
Jesus. I'm like a prophet. Prophet for
City Bank now. I'm like a prophet for
the peasants. And being tired is a real
thing. I think you've got to have a
little bit of sympathy for that.
>> All right, mate. Thanks for coming on.
Can I have a biscuit? No, these are
mine. I own these [__] biscuits.
>> James O'Brien, what a pleasure it is to
have you on the show. Are you right
About Everything?
>> Yes. I I don't I I find it utterly
discombobulating that you would even ask
such a racist question. I mean, I I
wrote a book on this a few years ago
called How to Always Be Right. And I'm
currently writing a um I'm currently
writing a sequel which probably YouTube
uh wannabe black shirts should should
consider reading. It's called How to
Stop Being Farright About Absolutely
Everything.
I don't remember the last time that
anybody called in on national radio and
and and proved me right proved me wrong
about anything. Whether that was about
Brexit, Brexit, Brexit, Brexit or or the
birth uh that is a curse of Nigel Farage
or or Donald Trump who is responsible
for absolutely everything that goes
wrong in this world up to and including
spoiler alert. The fact that I was
forced against my will when I was a
child to go to a private school
and 10 minutes past 10 is not even the
time.
James,
what's the most dangerous thing in
society? Is it the grooming gangs or is
it the people exploiting the grooming
gangs?
>> Well, I I I don't I don't think that you
could even argue that it's the grooming
gangs which do not actually even exist
or they are of course radically
exaggerated by uh wannabe stormtroopers
like yourselves. I mean, it's absolutely
discombobulating that you'd make an
exaggeration like that of such a
gargantuan scale. We are of course at
the moment facing an economic crisis
unprecedented
as a result of Brexit. So I don't think
you could argue we are of course worse
off for it. But do you two care about
it? Of course you don't. Of course you
don't. You couldn't give a sausage, not
a flying fig, not a cintilla. You
couldn't care less about the
consequences of your racist actions
questions, could you?
>> Well, why do you hate Brexit so much?
>> I think it is. Well, we all know the
reason for that. It has brought out of
the woodwork all of the fascists, all of
the racists, all of the bigots, all of
the footballification, the people who
you either stand with as we are might,
we are right, we are white. I I mean,
what else is there to say about it? I
don't think I've necessarily said enough
about it on national radio. Uh, but I
don't think there's anything really
really to like.
>> And uh, are you worried about climate
change? Well, I'd be far less worried
about it if you two uh uh would stop
spewing your Belgium bile every single
day with your verbal pollution and and
ripping a hole through the ozone layer.
>> We're ripping a hole in the ozone layer.
>> Well, I I think that's an inelectable
fact, mate. I don't think anybody would
dispute that. I mean I mean you you
constantly spew off information which no
spoiler alert you get from your auntie
Doris's Facebook page. Do you know I I
think we should do a phoneing. Should we
consider doing a phone in about whether
you two should just reduce your verbal
pollution to net zero? Should we do
that? 0345609
73. Uh and you will get through. The
lines are open now. You will get through
unless of course you are a disgusting uh
bilious toxic dump of a human being like
the two people in front of me from
trigonometry.
And and of course unless you are one of
the 51.9% who voted Brexit the fascists
and that's not an opinion, that's just
counting, mate. So the question that I
have for callers today is
should Constantine Kissing and Francis
Foster stop speaking all together and
how does it make you feel when they do?
How does it make you feel?
>> And James, how do you manage to stay so
humble?
>> When it's time to admit that I'm a mug,
basically when I when I know that I've
been taken for a mug and I mean
>> like with Jason Aardi, you mean? with
Jason Aldi. Although I wouldn't do
anything differently necessarily. I
wouldn't do a single thing differently.
That is humility at its finest. I I
don't know why I would have to. I mean,
I quite literally went from being uh
from drinking from the largest mug on
national radio to actually being uh the
largest mug on national radio. And I
think it's important to accept when
you're wrong, which is never in my case.
>> And and you've talked about fascism a
lot in this interview.
>> Yes.
>> Why would you say everyone's become a
fascist now?
>> Well, because they are. And I think the
onus is on you, mate, to actually prove
me wrong, which you would never do cuz I
am never wrong. You know, talking of
mugs, if I look look down at this mug
and I remove you two from your faces
from it, what do you see from that?
>> It'd be a red circle.
>> What do you see from that? Have you
guessed it yet?
>> Swastika.
>> It's almost You're on to something
there. It's almost the colors of
national socialism in Germany.
>> What do you think of that?
>> Red and white.
>> I'm going to repeat that again. Oh,
thank you.
>> I said if I remove your face, not your
hair
>> again, I can never be wrong.
>> Right. So, you'd get red, black, and
white.
>> Do I need to say any more than that?
Does that not prove my point that I'm
100% right and you two are fascists?
>> What does fascism mean, James?
>> I think you epitomize fascism.
You're making me late for the headlines,
mate.
>> James, thank you for coming on the show.
Uh, what would you say is the one thing
we're not talking about that we really
should be?
>> Brexit.
We don't talk about Brexit enough. I
think really we should be. And how all
the callers that call in are billious
toxic dumps of human beings.
Oddly, what's here with your headlines,
mate?
What I'm about to show you should make a
few very expensive brands quite
uncomfortable because it proves how much
of the price tag is just the name. Most
of you are skeptical of marketing on
principle and you're usually right to
be. So, here is a product built on the
opposite idea. This episode is sponsored
by dupe.com and the idea behind it is
refreshingly simple. A lot of what
you're paying for when you buy expensive
furniture, clothes, or accessories isn't
quality. It's the name on the label and
the marketing that got you to that page
in the first place. Dup.com finds you
the same look, the same quality, often
made in the same factory for a fraction
of the price. You paste in the link to
whatever it is you were eyeing or upload
a photo of it and DUP shows you close
matches that cost significantly less.
We've actually been using Jup here at
trigonometry. We searched dupe for
equipment we would have paid thousands
of pounds for and what it found instead
was something that did the same job for
hundreds. Using dupe.com is genuinely
simple. Go to dupe.com,
paste a product link or upload a photo
and it'll show you similar items for a
lot less. There's an app and a browser
extension too if you want it even
easier. No account needed, completely
free. dup.com. Go find yourself a better
price.
Here's Morgan. Welcome back to
Trigonometry. First question is um do
you feel like your humility has got in
the way of your success?
>> Well, hang on, hang on, hang on. First
of all, I just want to say I've noticed
that you two are wearing makeup, right?
I'm not wearing any makeup at all. So,
he looks maxing, aren't you? You know, I
learned that from, don't you? Special
guest of mine, Clvicular. Do you know
him?
>> Yeah. You a fan?
>> Well, listen, I've got a son that's his
age. He thinks I'm really cool. I'm
going to have a beer with him actually.
20 years old. Says I'm quite handsome.
Says I know how to meal. M look at this.
Do you know what meing is
that? Yeah. So, listen. You talk about
whether humility. I know what you're
referring to, right? What you're
referring to essentially is that I
upload on Instagram. Hang on. Don't
interrupt. I upload on Instagram every
single restaurant that nobody else can
afford. Right.
Hang on. Hang on. Hang on.
I upload every single one because I'm
trying to remind people that if they're
like me and they just wake up, which is
of course the name of one of my books
available in all fine bookstores
everywhere, they can also be like me.
You wish you like me, don't you? I can
see it in your eyes.
>> I suppose the question on everybody's
lips is what are your thoughts on Nigel
Farage?
>> Well, I'll tell you what I think of him.
He's a treacherous little worm. Right.
I'll tell you why. Right. He tried and
you both know it. I had an interview,
right, with Donald Trump. Good friend of
mine, by the way. Had an interview. I'm
friends with a lot of people. Every time
someone dies, I upload an image of them
with me.
So, I had an interview with Donald
Trump. And that little treacherous worm
tried to sabotage it, thinking that he's
better friends with him than me. And
that's clap trap. Utter [__] You
know that, right? Utter [__] Who
won the US apprentice? Me. Did he? No.
You wish you won it, didn't you? H could
you do that? By the way, do you condemn
Nigel Farage?
>> Well, just condemn him.
>> Well, just randomly condemn Nigel
Farage.
>> Yeah, condemn him.
>> 5 million quid or randomly can be for
any reason. What he did to me
treacherous little work.
Condemn him. Do you condemn him or not?
Hang on. Hang on. Simple question. Do
you condemn Nigel Farage or not?
>> No.
>> No. Well, I don't think we can continue
this conversation then. Well,
>> hang on.
>> No, you hang on. Don't tell me. No, I
tell people to hang on. You hang on for
me. Right.
>> Right.
>> Do you condemn Hamas?
>> Yes, I condemn.
>> You condemn Hamas. What about you?
>> Absolutely condemn Hamas.
>> All right. Okay. Continue.
>> Do you condemn Israel?
>> Well, I'll tell you what it is about
Israel. Right. Nobody's been more pro-
Israel than me. I've also sat on the
fence with all of it, right? because I
think it's important cutting edge
journalism which I suppose we'll get to
in a moment. I'm not going to condemn
Israel. I'm also not going to condone
it.
>> No.
>> So, speaking of journalism, do you think
your YouTube channel is cutting edge
journalism?
>> Well, I think it is and I think
everybody sees that and the reason for
that is as follows. Everybody knows that
I believe in free speech, right?
Uncensored for a reason. So, I think the
best way to have interviews and conduct
interviews, have five lunatics
screaming over each other, "Well, hang
on." So nobody can hear, right? Nobody
can hear a word that they're saying. And
I've got some of the best guests, not
only Clvicular we spoke about, brilliant
guests. We've also got people like Rabbi
Schmoolie, absolute pleasure to look at
and to hear. Got people like Andrew Tate
who are punch on absolutely everything,
knowing absolutely nothing about
absolutely anything. Right. Then we've
got people like Dave Smith, whose
knowledge, as you two know, is
unmatched. Doesn't think like a little
girl at all.
>> Cutting edge journalism.
>> Who is your favorite journalist, Pierce?
Well, it's me obviously
>> least unexpected answer in history.
>> My brother who's a colonel in the armed
forces agrees with me. What do you think
of that? What do you think of that? I'll
tell you why I'm the best one. Because
nobody nobody in the journalist business
delegates like I do. I've been saying
for a long time that Israel needs to
open its border. Right? I've been
calling for that. Right? You know that
now. If Israel opens the Gaza border,
I'd be the very first to delegate
somebody to go and check it out.
What do you think of that? And then I'd
get on my get behind my desk and I'd
talk about it and I'd tell you about it.
I won't go there. No. Why should I? Not
only that, I've also got I also bring
you aesthetic beauty. Did you see when I
touched Ronaldo's abs? Did you see that?
What do you think of that? What do you
think of it? Who else has touched
Ronaldo's abs?
>> People, I imagine.
>> Yeah, mainly Ronaldo, actually.
>> Mainly him. Yeah. Not everyone gets
aroused by it. I do.
>> Ronaldo does. I'm not ashamed of it.
Speaking of uh beauty and being aroused,
would you ever go on a date with Megan
Markle?
>> Absolutely not. No way. You know what?
She stalked me. She sent me messages
non-stop begging me to go out with her.
She's picking for it. Basically on her
knees. I said, "I don't want to be
whipped. Where I'm from, I'm a man,
right? Alpha male. I'm not a wuss, but I
do know a gingerbread prince who wants
to be whipped." So I shudder in a taxi
and I said, "Don't whip him."
But what do you think of that? Meghan
Markle wanted me. I inspire the youth.
>> I mean, there's a lot of people, Pier,
who say that you really fancy her and
that's the way that you behave the way
that you did with her.
>> No, no, it's not true. She fancied me.
She wouldn't stop. I think it was my
slim fitted shirts that she was
attracted to. I've been working out
recently. What do you think of this?
Been working out, haven't you?
>> Can you tell? Hang on. Can you tell?
>> Pierce. Pierce. Uh, what's
>> Hang on.
>> Continue,
>> Pierce.
>> Hang on. Go.
>> Am I allowed to talk now?
>> Oh, yeah.
>> You sure?
>> Well, I can censor or uncensor. Of
course.
>> Makes sense. What's the final thing?
See, I can't even ask the question now.
You interrupted me so many times. What's
the thing that we're not talking about
that we really should be?
>> Cristiano Ronaldo's abs and my brother
who was a colonel in the armed forces.
My brother's a colonel in the armed
forces.
>> Really?
>> Yeah. Nobody talks about it.
>> Russell Brand, welcome to trigonometry.
How long have you been a Christian for?
And did it have anything to do with the
allegation?
>> Before I answer that question, I would
like to take the opportunity to
penetrate both of you with a little bit
of prayer to the Lord. So, I'd like you
to do me a favor and just grope your h
hands together and just flaccidate
yourselves and close your eyes and do
not open them until I've insticated you
after I've whispered prayer into the
Lord's earhole.
Heavenly Father, shine both of your
breasts on these two podcasters, Francis
Foster and Constantine Kissing, and
forgivicate them for they know not what
they do. They do not know what they do.
And I wonder if you could provide them,
Lord, with the uh wisdomization and
wankulation to prevent them to prevent
them from falling for the titillating
temptations that are made against them.
To put before me a clitony of questions
that have been put before them and
squirt me with those questions that have
been put before them, no doubt, by big
farmer and big government, which are
designed, of course, to assassinate my
character with which you have
impregnated me. Lord, please give me the
strength to be their rock. Please uh let
us be there for one another to support
one another to guide one another so that
when I when they open their eyes upon my
instructication
they may accept as I exclaim that I am
by God's grace their new Lord. You may
now open your eyes.
You may now proceed to procreate your
question.
>> Well I guess you didn't answer my first
question Russell which is a lot of
people
>> Yes. and looking at your new found
conversion to Christianity and thinking
to themselves, well, does it have
anything to do with the impending court
case?
>> Well, listen, becoming a Christian is
not something that I think that you
actually do. I don't think I became a
Christian. I think I was born a
Christian. I am a bit I guess you could
say people would describe as a born
again Christian. But the truth is, it is
only when you understand and realize
without the sweet milk of the Lord,
you're not able to germinate. you're not
able to inseminate people and fertilize
the world with his love and his word and
wankify it. So it's not that I take
offense or anything like that by the
question ultimately we're here to have a
dialogue but all of us but I do take a
little bit of cumbrage with the idea
that I may have actually converted to
Christianity in order to deflect or or
distract from any of my case. You got to
understand I'm a very different person
to what I was what I was when a few
years ago I was a wanker. I'm a very
different person now. I'm a God-fearing
testicularizing man and I have elevated
and I have elevated to make it my life's
missionary to amplify his word and
fertilize the world with his word in a
moment of love and passion.
>> Do you have anything to say about the
court case? You're facing serious
allegations. Russell
>> after I become a Christian in seven
days, right? I was able to internalize
and understand that this is not actually
a trial by social media or media or even
the the the criminal justice system or
the authorities that be. No, rather this
is a trial that has been sentiated to me
by God himself. A trial. What a thing to
embrace. What a thing to love and to
cherish. I'm no longer I'm no longer
frightened of the long rod of the Lord.
I actually welcome the long hardened
swelled rod of the Lord to spankate me
if I need that. If that what we could
all do is a little bit of a spiritual
spankulation now and again. And that is
what I want from the Lord. See, you've
got to understand essentially by making
that little change in that moment of
meditation. What I'm able to do that
mind shift, I'm able, I believe, to
lubricate this entire process. I'm able
to thrust myself into the spotlight of
God, which is I like to call it the
spiritual G-spot.
And do you think these
allegations
>> Yes.
>> Uh they've been
>> Lord save these two poor souls
>> engineered in an attempt to silence you
in your message.
>> Well, it's no coincidence to me and it's
nothing new to me that the government
would try to silence me. What I actually
have been describing this as recently is
that I believe that this is part of a
governmental freesome strategy that has
been employed against me. So the first
part of the freesome freesome strategy
is the accusation itself being alleged
against me. That allegation is there in
order to scare people in order to
convince people that they need
protection or cond or condomization.
They need that protection. That's what
they need. And that is the ultimate
thing which is going to convince people
to perform certain acts that under
normal circumstances they wouldn't
necessarily perform. And so once they
have got you there, they've got they've
got you in the second part of the
threesome strategy that is control. They
convince you that you need protection
from somebody like me and then you need
to be controlled. So they've got you in
that position physically, literally and
metaphorically bent over on all fours,
stripped down to your bare nakedity so
they can perform their final action and
thrust themselves into you. And that
final action is something which I
actually talk about in my book how to
become a Christian in seven days.
There's actually a chapter on it. It's
called total sex appropriation and
conomination. They completely conominate
you and that. So I'm no stranger to all
of this strategy. It's nothing new to
me. I know that the government and wants
me to not speak out against big
government. It doesn't want me to speak
out against big farmer. It doesn't want
me to speak out against the industrial
military climax. Doesn't want me to. It
doesn't want me to scrutize against any
of these people. And now that I've
liated myself, I realize that I will
continue to act. Doesn't matter what
they try and do to silence me. I will
continue to act as God's fallopian tube,
his little conduit to fertilize this
world with love and passion,
spiritual passion.
>> Um, do you think it's possible that
you're a bit of a narcissist, Russell?
>> I think it's an interesting question. I
think I think back in the day when I was
a wanker, I think maybe I was a little
bit of a a narcissist. I think that
narcissism is always very confusing to
me when I was growing up because I used
to see I used to look at politics and
I'd see you had all these isms you had
progressivism, liberalism, conservatism,
you know, fascism, communism and all
that. I also found it a little bit
quickated. And so what I what I actually
did I thought well there's no there's no
ideology that suits the the headers
which is what I was when I was a wanker.
So I created the wankiology of wankism.
>> What sorry to sorry to interrupt Russell
sorry I'm getting a bit lost in the
linguistics here. very, you know,
articulate.
>> Yes.
>> What What did you You were a What?
Sorry.
>> I was a wankist.
>> What's a wankist?
>> It's someone who It's a hedenist. It was
more in my salacious date.
>> Ah, it's a more Yeah.
>> Someone who Exactly. Okay.
>> I love how this communication with love.
I love you at the moment. I really do.
I'm taking this moment to love you. I'm
looking at you, loving you. I'm praying
for you. I'll forgive you.
>> Feels very authentic. Thank you.
>> It's very authentic.
Just let me just take a moment.
I love you, Lord.
Thank you. So, what was I saying? So, I
traded in wankism for fankism. I'm now
creating my new ideology because I
appreciate the blessings that the Lord
himself has given me, the bonafide
blessings. So, yeah, I traded that in.
Now, was I a bit of a narcissist? Yeah,
maybe it was a little bit of a wank
plank of my wankyology, but not anymore.
>> And would you would you like to still be
making Hollywood movies?
Well, absolutely not. I don't want to,
you see, I want nothing to do with
Hollywood because listen, back when I
was writing, I did enjoy it, but I don't
I don't crave those things anymore. I
don't want superficial things. I don't
want money. It's not interesting to me.
All these all these things that really
don't mean much. They give you a little
bit of instant gratification.
Having said that, there was something
interesting that happened that I don't
really talk about too publicly very
often, but I will I will share it with
you lads just because I'm I'm forgiving
both of you at the moment. I will say
that I did submit a script recently to
Hollywood. Some agents that were talking
to me back in the day. They don't talk
to me anymore. I submittiated a script
where I thought, well, what if I write
something that's going to do good,
that's going to spread love, that's
going to warn people about the impending
threats that are surrounding us?
Artificial intelligence, humanoids,
robots, things that we cannot even
comprehend, let alone understand. So,
what if I write something like that now
to do good in the world? And I actually
wanted it to as a warning. You know, I
wanted to be like kind of warning people
like a spin-off of the Terminator that
we're about to be enslaved to a master.
And I think they actually liked the
agents actually liked it in Hollywood,
but I don't think they accepted it.
Probably because of the name that I
wanted to come up with.
>> What's the name?
>> Masturbator.
>> You know, Russell, you you keep saying
that you forgive us. What? Why do you
need to forgive us? What have we done
wrong?
>> It's about vacaseliniating this
conversation, making it very
jurorability, making it very durable.
And I feel that from forgiveness you can
learn to love me. I can actually
inseminate you with holy water right
now. And I do that mentally and
spiritually. I do that mentally and
spiritually. I'm not talking about in a
physical space. Those days are behind
me. I'm talking about in a spiritual
place. And I actually am inseminating
you with holy water right now. And I'm
praying for you. And I love you. And I
think that everything that we do right
now, think about all the joy that we're
bringing to the world right now. Think
about that. Imagine if you hadn't asked
me that question right now. I wouldn't
have been able to copulate you, which is
what I do. Do you you seem a bit
obsessed with sex to me, Russell. Do you
reckon that's a fair criticism?
>> That was just they were back in my days,
like I said, when I was a wanker.
Wankilutely not anymore. And I think
it's quite a wankagonistic question that
you're asking me there. I really do. I
think now it's not about sex. Of course,
the Lord encourages sex, but in
spiritual way. And that's how I feel
about you. I want to have spiritual sex
with both of you now on this table.
Please.
Do you think you're a bit of a cult
leader, Russell?
>> I think that I'm the only person who has
spoken out against the COVID 19 vaccine
and I think people follow me and I think
that is what the big government doesn't
like. That is what the big tech
companies don't like. The industrial
ministry climax, like I said earlier,
that is what they don't like. So people
follow me and what do they do? They ban
me. They stop me from talking. They stop
me trying to silenceify me. That's what
they try and do. But they're not going
to succeed because I love them too much.
And even if they do, I will do it with a
smile.
>> And uh Russell, final question. as you
know on the show is always the same.
What's the one thing we're not talking
about that we should be?
>> Certainly how to become a Christian in
seven days that by reading that I want
to say on a serious note you will learn
to condomize yourself. When I say
condomize yourself I mean protect
yourselves. You will surround your
entire being your entire body with
protection a layer of protection and
you'll be able to think about your
words. you'll be able to think about the
consequences of your words and actions
in some other people's cases, court
cases.
>> Uh Russell, final question actually for
me is what's your favorite Bible passage
and why?
>> Right. I was happy that you asked that.
>> Russell, I can't help noticing that's
not a Bible. It's a copy of The Wealth
of Nations by Adam Smith.
>> Yeah. And I think it's important to read
out my favorite passage from that, if
you'll allow me. It was put upon the
same footing
with gold and silver minds which the
Lord without a special clause in the
charter of the Lord's word and his
shepherd were never supposed to be
comprehendiated
with sexual being in the general grant
of the land lands the fertile lands and
the eggs
though minds of lead copper tin and coal
were as things of smaller consequences
conomination smaller consequences is
that's why you should read my book.
>> How to become a Christian in seven days.
>> Thanks for coming on.
>> My pleasure. My spiritual insemination
pleasure.
>> Elon, we've been trying to make this
happen for a very long time. Thanks for
coming on the show.
>> Yeah. Yeah. It is my pleasure.
>> Well, it's great great to have you on.
Uh would you say autism is your
superpower?
I'd say that uh having autism allows you
to say pretty pretty much whatever you
want
and get away with it. And and when when
when you also have uh the I mean when
you also have the world's the largest
social media platform and and the
biggest in the universe, uh you you're
all kind of screwed.
So yeah, autism is a superpower.
>> Superpower.
>> Awesome.
>> And And how are you able to do all the
things that you do and still be on on
Twitter 24/7? X. Sorry.
>> Yeah. Yes.
>> So when when people ask me that, I
always just say when you're I'm not
actually human. uh when you're kind of
made up of humanoid uh and South African
human and artificial intelligence,
you're you're actually able to do a lot
more uh than people think. Uh so yeah,
autism, humanoid, and artificial
intelligence, not being human, uh that's
kind of how I'm able to do it. So yeah.
>> Yeah.
>> And a personal question if I may.
>> Uh how many kids do you have? It's kind
of like my bank balance. You can't
really calculate. Uh I could have
another one right now. I can actually
hear in the artificial intelligence that
is in me now that I have another one
right now. Probably in the trillions.
So yeah, I'd also like to admonish you
for even asking questions that really
don't concern you. as a the richest man
in the world, I can just tell you to go
[__] yourself. So,
>> you can?
>> Yeah, that's what I'm going to do.
Awesome. Go [__] yourself. So,
>> I mean, what is it like being the
richest man in the world?
>> Well, that's that's the beauty of it.
You can just tell everybody to go [__]
themselves and and you don't really have
to worry about it. Also,
it kind of gives me me the the time that
I need to focus on things that are
really important. Uh, like standup
comedy. Yeah. Yeah. I I get to I just
thought of a a joke now.
Yeah. I'm going to test my material on
you now. So, so what do you call a a a
place in space on Mars uh where really
cool people hang out? Mosbar.
Yeah, I Yeah, it's really awesome
comedy. I just Yeah. Yeah. So, I I just
thought of another one, too. Uh Yeah. I
I just thought uh So, what do you call a
bank balance of of a trillion dollars?
Yeah. Yeah. An elongated bank balance.
I'm gonna tweet that. Post it. Post it.
Sorry. Awesome joke.
comes back. Yeah.
>> Why do you support restore?
>> I think I support the people who
actually want to make the United Kingdom
great again and reverse some of the
things that your governments have done
over the years. And I think Restore is
the only
uh party that's going to do that. I
mean, look at what your your your
country has become.
I mean, look at Luton, where my friend
Tom Robson is from. I mean, it used to
be a paradise and now
and now it is the Lou T. Great joke. Uh,
only the British would understand that.
Uh, and and I thought of another joke
actually. Can I test that? Yeah. So, an
Englishman, an Irishman, a Scotsman, and
a and a Welshman walk into a bar in
Luton. And they say, "We we want a
drink." And the bartender says, "Uh, no,
please leave." And they say, "Why? We we
just want to drink." And he says, "No,
you don't understand. We don't serve
foreigners
because the British people have
foreigners in Luton now." So yeah,
awesome job.
>> And finally, just just a personal
question for you, Elon. I mean, how many
baby mamas do you have at the moment?
>> It's it's another thing that I don't
actually even have the answer to. And
again, I'd like to admonish you for
asking things that are just personal.
And again, I will tell you to go [__]
yourself. You couldn't even calculate
it. Even if you even if you wanted to,
you couldn't do it. The only thing that
that could do that would be uh a special
chip of artificial intelligence that's
largely in my brain. Yeah. Yeah. Elon,
what's the one thing we're not talking
about that we should be?
>> Um,
yeah, it's a good question. Probably
Yeah, probably AOC
and and and the left and also the trans
movement. Yeah. How the the work mind
virus that has destroyed our planet and
universe. Uh so
>> and what about AOC?
>> She well she she tried to come on to me
a few times and some [__] and I just
I mean she's she looks pretty good.
But um I'm not I'm not I'm not
particularly interested in her anymore.
So
>> would you have a baby with AOC?
That that would what if I had a baby
with with AOC? I just thought of another
joke.
What do you call a a a baby born born to
AOC and Elon Musk? Yeah.
>> A trillion dollar baby.
Yeah. Any baby born to Elon Musk
actually. So yeah. Awesome joke.
President Trump, welcome to
Trigonometry. Uh, first question, why
are you the greatest president in
history?
>> Uh, because I've done so much for the
country and you know that better than
anybody. We have the ballroom. We're
fixing the ballroom. The ballroom's
going to get done. And you know that uh
you know we've had the uh UFC We had the
UFC fight. You guys saw that, right?
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah. We had that. We had that. It was
just an incredible event. Some say the
likes of which the world has never seen
actually when you think about it. And
it's not even close. And uh we're just
getting so much done. You know, people
things that people never thought were
possible. They thought it was never
possible. Uh but it is possible. And I'm
getting it done. And the most important
thing, you know what it is, right? The
ballroom. We got to get the ballroom.
>> I was going to say the Middle East.
>> No, no, no, no, no. Why don't you just
shut your mouth? Why don't you just be
quiet? Why don't you be quiet and listen
to your favorite president?
Uh it's the ballroom. The American
people, they voted for it and they want
it more than anything. They don't want
all these other things. cuz they don't
want to talk about the Middle East.
That's people like you on your stupid
podcast. Uh just putting a war effort
down because you're a bad person
actually.
>> How are you going to bring peace to the
Middle East though?
>> Well, I actually already have and
everybody knows that. A lot of people
are saying it except you and you uh you
know they have the Abraham Accords.
You're familiar with that, right? Maybe
you've heard of it. A little thing
called the Abraham course. Uh they
probably haven't even heard of it. Uh so
much nicer to say Abraham than Abraham.
Right? I have Hamas, you know, they
calling me up every day. They say, "Sir,
sir, there's too much peace here in the
Middle East. There's too much peace. We
can't deal with it." I say, "No, you're
going to have peace. You know, we
created the board of peace." And
actually, Hamas is starting to get a
little bit bored of peace actually. Uh
so I already have done that. And when
you think about it as well, the Straits
of Hormuz and the Iranian army totally
and utterly obliterated. And the Straits
of Hormuz isn't the Straits of Hormuz
anymore. No, no, it's uh the Straits of
America.
>> Yeah, that's true. That's true.
Actually,
>> it's still closed though, right?
>> No, it's totally open. Uh, you know,
that's just a nasty question. You're
such a nasty guy. Uh, we've opened it
and there's more shipping. You know,
they thought it was going to be closed.
They thought this isn't going to open
again. I got it open. You understand
that? Or are you a stupid person? Are
you stupid?
>> I don't.
>> You just must be a dumb person. The
straits of America is open. And uh you
know that better than anybody. You see,
he doesn't want to say it. He doesn't
want to say it, but he knows it's true,
right?
>> No.
>> Yeah. He doesn't want to say it. He
doesn't want
>> Do you feel the war in the Iran war was
a good idea?
>> Uh yeah, I do. I do actually. I think it
was a very good idea. Look, it's very
simple. Iran can never be allowed a
nuclear weapon. And you know, I hear all
this negative negative talk on your
podcast. You're being very nasty to me,
both of you actually, saying it was a
bad idea. Oh, Donald Trump shouldn't
have done this. No, no, I had to do it.
And you know, I also hear negativity
about the Russia. Remember that little
war? Russia in Ukraine. Ukraine. Let me
ask you a question. What? You're from
Moscow originally, right?
>> Yeah. I've done my research on you. Why
didn't you tell me about what Putin was
going to do? Why didn't you tell me
about it? Like the Japanese, they never
told me about Pearl Harbor. You could
have done it. And as for you, you know,
you're Venezuelan. I called you. I said
to you, I said, "Uh, do you know where
Maduro is? Do you remember that phone
call?" I called it the perfect phone
call. And it was a perfect phone call,
actually. And it's not even close. And
you said to me, "No, no, no, sir." You
sounded like Emanuel Mcronone. You said,
"No, no, sir. Can I give you the
coordinates?" I didn't even want your
help. I didn't need your help. Uh but
you were very nasty to me. And the
Iranian war has been a wonderful success
and it's winding down anyway. By the
way, you're such nasty people.
>> We've been trying to get you on
trigonome trigonometry for so long.
>> That's right.
>> Why is it taking you so long to
>> Well, because you've been so nasty.
>> We've been nasty.
>> You've been so bad. You've been so bad,
the both of you. And all you do is
spread bad news. And half the toast's
not even fake. And your ratings are
terrible, by the way. Why should I give
you ratings? You call me up and you say,
"Sir, sir, please. We want you to come
and trigonometry."
I'm actually doing this as a favor to a
friend. I don't want to be here for you.
Uh, you don't really deserve it. You're
actually worse than Rosie O'Donnell. Uh,
yeah. I mean, it's pretty bad. Pretty
Yeah, you're worse. You're worse,
actually. Some say worse. A lot of
people are saying that, actually, and
you know that better than anybody.
Uh,
>> why are we worse than Rosie O'Donnell?
I'm actually genuinely offended
>> because you're just disgusting people.
And she was also disgusting. She was
also a disgusting person and is a
disgusting person. Look, Iran could
never be allowed a nuclear weapon,
right? So, we had to go to war with
them. And all you do is just talk badly
about it. I don't appreciate that very
much at all. And I will tariff the hell
out of you, by the way.
>> Um,
>> he thinks I'm joking. I'm not joking at
all. I will tariff the hell out of you.
>> I don't think you're joking. I think
you're being deadly serious, Mr. By the
way, the studio is a [__] hole.
>> What's wrong with the studio?
>> It reminds me of uh some of these [__]
hole countries that we have to do
business with. It's just quite similar.
I don't know. I just
>> I just get a bad feeling about it. Just
a bad feeling.
>> I thought it's the greatest studio in
the world.
>> No, it's a [__] hole.
>> It's a [__]
>> Yeah. You should have granite.
>> You should have marble. You should have
gold. You don't have any of that.
>> Uh it's fake. Actually, everything about
it is In fact, you're fake.
>> Yeah. You're not even here. you fake.
>> Are are you even happy to be in the UK,
Mr. President?
>> Uh well, I will say that it's not
recognized. It's not recognizable. That
I will say and you know that better than
anybody. You walk down the street. I
don't know who I'm looking at. Everybody
is a man or a woman or they claim to be
a man or a woman. You have men uh in
women's sports here, right? And your new
prime minister, I mean your old one, he
was not Churchill that I will say. I
think your new one's worse.
>> Would agree with you on that?
>> I think he's worse, actually. It's a
very good point, Mr. President.
>> The only thing that would be worse is if
you two ever run for politics. You
better not do that.
>> Uh yeah,
>> we won't.
>> No, we we definitely won't. I I mean,
>> I'm I'm quite taken back by that.
>> You're in a state of shock.
>> I'm in a state of shock.
>> You're in a state of shock. You know,
it's so pathetic.
>> And there there's a lot of rumors at the
moment that you're going to be running
for a third term. Uh, are you gonna be
on this show and quash those rumors?
>> Well, I might. Yeah, I haven't revealed
that yet. I think a lot of people will
be happy about that. Uh, you wouldn't be
happy about it. Uh, because
>> be unconstitutional.
>> Well, actually, there's a whole debate
about that. Nobody likes to talk about
it, but it's true. Uh, there's nothing
unconstitutional about it. By the way,
you're British. You nobody cares what
the hell you think about anything
anymore. And they haven't for a long
time, and you know that. But yeah, uh I
have to run for a third term
potentially. We'll see. We'll see. And
the reason is, you know why, right? We
got to get the ballroom done. We got to
get that ball. We got to get that
ballroom. We really do. Uh and I'm
putting you on notice if I do because I
will come into the studio in a third
term and I will bomb the [__] out of
both of you. You know that, right? He
knows that.
>> Uh and on that note, um what
>> have you ever had a missile fall on your
head? You You've never felt it myself. A
big beautiful B2 bomber straight on your
heads. Think of it. That would be
beautiful, right? Two B2 bombers on both
of your heads.
>> I I don't think it will be beautiful. Um
I I'm going to be honest, but
nevertheless, um
>> Mr. President, I don't understand the
hostility.
>> Well, you're just nasty people. You're
just bad people. I don't know what else
to say about it. Everything I do, it's
uh it's Iran's butt. No, no, no. We
think closing the border.
>> Excuse me. No, no, excuse me. Excuse me.
>> You close the border.
>> Excuse me. No, you don't think that's
good. You don't think you were
criticizing it. Don't be so nasty. Don't
be so rude. Don't be rude in front of
your friend here. Why don't you just be
a nice person for once if it's possible?
Go ahead. What do you want to say? He's
going to ask some stupid question now,
right?
>> I was just going to say I think it's
wonderful that you were able to close
the border. You ended illegal
immigration into the US.
>> I did do that.
>> Give you credit for that. I think that's
great.
>> But it's true. You know, we've been
skeptical about the war in Iran.
>> Well, why are you skeptical about it?
Why don't you tell me to my fa to my
face? What did you say to my face right
now?
>> What is it about the war in Iran that
you're so against?
>> Well, first of all,
>> do you want new Do you want him to have
a nuke?
>> No.
>> They can never have a nuke.
>> I agree.
>> Do you agree?
>> Yes.
>> So, what are you against?
>> Well, on a political level,
>> he's so stupid. I don't know why your
friends will. He's so stupid.
>> You're calling me low IQ.
>> You're so low IQ. You're worse than
Tucker Carlson, actually.
>> Worse.
>> You're worse. You're worse. I bet. You
know what? I'm going to in my third
term, I'm going to call this place when
I invade it and take it over. I'm going
to call it Trig America. And it's going
to be higher IQ than you two. Especially
you. I don't know why you hang out with
him. You're so low IQ.
>> Who would you replace us with?
>> Uh, that's a good question. Probably
Jared Kushner and Steve Whit.
I probably would. Uh, but you were
saying why you're against it and you can
say you can continue. So on a political
level uh you look said you said yourself
you might lose the midterms and then
you'll be impeached but also in a
practical sense you're clearly losing
the war.
>> Well again how am I losing the the war
is won. It's one ongoing.
>> It's not ongoing. That's fake news.
>> Look when you think about it. I have
beaten Iran and I've beaten and beaten
and beaten the hell out of them.
>> And people say oh no it's over. And
people should say, well, uh, people say,
well, maybe you should use the new kind
of, or maybe you're going to hit them
again. There's no need. The straits are
open. Uh, shipping is better than it's
ever been before. And it's way better,
by the way. And it's not even close.
Your prices are down.
>> Uh, people are getting eggs. People
getting eggs now. People are eating eggs
in in abundance. There's so many eggs.
So many So many eggs are coming through
the straits of America from Iran, right?
Nobody thought that was possible. You
never thought it was possible.
>> I didn't realize we imported eggs from
Iran.
>> Well, we do, quite frankly. And uh we
actually import everything through and
it's not it's not from Iran anymore.
Very soon it's going to be America. It's
going to be the it's going to be another
state. 52nd state after after Canada
actually when you count that or actually
53rd when you count Greenland. Uh it's
going to be a beautiful thing. So you
better watch it. I'm putting you on
notice. You both better watch it, right?
>> Um and what's the one thing that we're
not talking about, Mr. President, that
we should be.
>> What a terrific job I'm doing. What a
terrific job I'm doing. People don't
think of it. People don't like to talk
about what a fantastic job I'm doing.
They don't like to say it. You know why,
right?
>> Not
>> because they're worried about the
elections. You have the de Democrats. I
call them Democrats. You You two are
like Democrats.
Low IQ. If you were in America, you'd be
Democrats. That I will say. Or you'd
probably be with Tucker Carlson and
probably even more low IQ than him. Or
Candace. Cookie. I call her kooky
Candace. Right.
>> Yeah. We don't like her or Tucker
either.
>> Well, then we can agree on that. We can
be friends on that. we can uh at least
we can have a bit of an agreement. But
uh yeah, they don't they don't want me
to run again and they don't want to
cooperate. Uh they're so dumb.
>> Have you enjoyed this interview, Mr.
President?
>> Well, I will say that it is uh you've
given me a fair hearing. I will say what
that I don't think you did when I'm not
here, which says something about you,
too. You're basically cowards. Uh but I
think uh yeah, I think it's been
pleasant, but I won't come again. I
wouldn't come here again. No. No. Uh, I
mean, England is totally unrecognizable.
I don't know where I am even half the
time. And your coffee is terrible, by
the way. In fact, your mugs are
terrible. Everything about you is
terrible.
Quite frankly,
Thomas Robinson,
>> welcome back to Sugaromy.
>> Yeah. Pleasure to be here.
>> So, what didn't we talk about the first
time we had you on that we should have
talked about?
>> We didn't talk about my friends from
London. Yeah. I'm a journalist from
Luton.
I had a friend called Abdullah Duck.
Yeah. He was Donald Duck in in the past.
He was a mate of mine, convert to
radical Islam. Now he's Donald Abdullah
Duck. We don't talk about that. I only
know this cuz I'm a journalist.
Other mates of mine. We don't talk about
him. Muhammad Gizmo. Just used to be
Gizmo from the Kremlins. He's now
Muhammad Gizmo. It's [__] terrorist,
mate. Why are you worried about Islam
and its effect on our country, Tommy?
>> Never said that. All I've ever said,
I've said that radical Islam is the
problem. People are coming up to me in
the street saying, "Do you want to
fight?" Yeah. Why are you saying this
about Islam? I don't actually say
anything about Islam. If you look at
everything what I've said, I've actually
said only good things about Islam. I
just don't know radical Islam. That's
all. I know that cuz I'm from Luton.
Tommy, you've obviously got into a lot
of altercations and fights and you seem
to have kind of, you know, jumpy energy
a little bit.
I'm not perfect. Yeah,
>> that's a fair point.
>> So, what's your question?
>> I was just going to say, you know, do
you seek out the confrontation? Are you
a violent person by nature?
>> I I have got I've got to walk. Listen,
I'm from London, so I'm not perfect,
right? I was grown up I grew up as a
lad. Fighting was a thing. But when I'm
in the street walking on my own, I've
got to film everything. People don't
understand. I don't walk around
security. People come up to me and want
to fight. If they want to fight, I will
do it. But I'm trying to avoid it. I
don't try to get in [__] fights,
mate. People come up to me in a
confrontation cuz they don't like my
journalism cuz they know it's too good
and they don't want my rallies. So yeah,
there seems to be a lot of sniffing
going on here. Uh Tommy, there's a lot
of people have insinuated it might be uh
something a bit nefarious. What what do
you say to
>> people from Luton? Sniff
especially journalists from Lutonh. We
sniff
and how do you see yourself? Do you see
yourself as a freedom fighter, an
activist, a journalist? What are you
Tommy?
>> So a lot of the journalism that I do is
online. All the stuff that I do, all the
tweets and all all that people call it
hate. Thanks to Elon Musk, I've got free
speech again. Got to remember I was put
in solitary confinement sniffing. I was
put in solitary confinement. Now that
I'm out, I think my my goal is just to
just to wake people up. That's all my
goal is. Just wake people up. That's it.
I'll be voting for Rupert Low. So yeah.
Would you ever go back to Luton?
>> I always go back to Loot. Loot's my
hometown. I [__] love Luton. But when
I was growing up in Luton, there was
about three mosques. Now there's about 1
million of them. So yeah. And I don't
exaggerate. Nothing that I say online is
exaggerated. Yeah. So yeah, believe what
you want.
>> Tommy, final question is always the
same. What's the one thing we're not
talking about that we really should be?
>> Radical Islam and Donald Abdullah Duck.
Yeah, a mate of mine who converted to
radical Islam. That's it.
>> So Francis, welcome back. It's been a
while since we did one of these. Um, how
have you been and what have you made of
of, you know, everything that's been
going on? Well, first of all, I just
want to say that I hate Argentina. I
hate Argentina,
the the lying, the cheating, and we
don't we don't talk about enough. We not
Nobody's talking about the arrogance
about Argentina,
and also what's been going on in the
news with Andy Burnham. Has he ended
homelessness? No. Has he delivered on
any of the things that he says he will?
Of course he hasn't. and we don't talk
about it. And his first PMQ's absolutely
awful. He should probably read my book.
Uneducated.
So, Constantine, how do you see the
political situation in the UK at the
moment?
>> I think it's a [__] show, mate. I think
it's only getting worse. And it's
interesting because if you speak to
people like Peter Hitchens, you realize
actually Peter was kind of right about
everything. I don't know whether you
agree with that, but I think Peter was
right about everything. And then you
look at what's been happening in the
news. I don't know whether you watch the
brain rot of the Candace Owens and
Andrew Wilson debate, but it was
literally just her talking about facts
as if they were facts, but really they
were just her [__] feelings. It takes
me a lot of restraint on X not to
respond to things like saying Candace is
a complete [__] I have to restrain
myself all the time, but I managed to do
it.
>> So,
who is the worst? Is it Candice? Is it
Tucker? Is it Nick Fuentes?
>> I mean, they're all just as bad as each
other. They're all kooky. You've got
Kooky Candice. You've got Nasty Nick.
And who was the other one?
>> Uh, Tucker.
>> I don't think I even want to. You've got
I mean I mean, he's just a a cokehead. I
mean, he's clearly just a cokehead. He's
just online all the time. And we've
actually seen that in this studio today,
haven't we?
Tony Lapidus, thank you for all those
hilarious impressions. Thanks for coming
on, mate.
>> My pleasure. Thank you for having me.
>> Yeah, it was really, really good. How
How did you get so good at all of these
different characters?
>> Um, well, I've been doing impressions
since I was about the size of this mug.
Um, you know, they started all starts in
the playground. All starts with uh doing
>> You took a lot of beatings when you were
a kid.
>> Many beatings. Well, no, they should
have seen the other guys. Um, but I you
know, it was all started in the
playground. A lot of family members. Um,
anybody who got too close to me made the
mistake of getting too close to me, uh,
got impersonated and that's and so
that's why the teachers absolutely hated
me growing up. Um, but the pupils, my
classmates liked me. So, yeah, just for
that.
>> And how do you create a really good
impression? What is it? What is the art
of a good impression?
>> Um, I think firstly it's always the
voice. Um but in in my case particularly
I think one of the things I'm I'm quite
good at is uh embodying the people and
changing my face almost. That's why I I
tried to like so when I when I did
>> um Milo you know his entire face changes
um and when I do you know I do some
boxers and people like that I changed my
face for like um Tyson Fury and the
people I imitate in the sports world.
And I always think that even where
sometimes the voice might be lacking a
little bit if you move your body like
them. Um if you if you change your
facial expressions like them, you can
really make up for you can really
compensate for that. But the goal is
always the voice. So um for me it's not
actually about studying them. I don't
try and study them. What I do is I
listen to them. I started off listening
to your podcast just listening out of a
matter of interest and uh eventually
something just kind of clicks. some you
can't even do in the beginning, but the
more you just listen, just absorb them.
Um, suddenly if you look at, for
example, the Peter Hitchens impression
that I did, my very first one just isn't
the same one as it is now. And that
applies for a lot of them. So, it's just
about letting it in and then realizing
you talk to yourself a lot as well,
>> which makes people think you're mad.
>> Yeah.
>> Your Peter Hitchens is really good. Uh,
there was actually a question I think
from our supporters on Substack, which
was which one of us is harder to do an
impression of? And I have to say, I
think it must be me. Your Francis, it
seems to me like a lot more on the
money.
>> Yeah, I think you're right. I think
you're right. I actually remember your
very first reaction to my uh to my
impression of you. You said, "Why do I
sound American?" Yeah.
>> Um whether I still do.
>> Well, I don't think you do in the bit
that we did for Substack. I don't think
I your me sounds American.
>> Oh, okay. So,
>> I think is there something about me
that's just a bit hard to imitate or
bland or what? No, but but again, you're
somebody who I I think I do your body
language better than I do the voice. Um
I think people can see what I'm getting
at with the voice, even if it's not
100%. Um I think people see I think
people people online are actually very
nice and encouraging. You know, they'll
say like, "This one's improving, that
one's improving." They've always liked
yours. Yours is yours has just been
easier. The body language is is is is
actually funnier. Why exaggerate? I
mean, I tell you're not constantly doing
that with your glasses. I've just made
you do that for no reason. Um um I have
picked up on little things that that
that you'll say like we're not talk
about enough. But there's there's a part
of me that actually doesn't like doing
them and I'll tell you why. Because I
always feel that once people have heard
that it's kind it's almost a bit of a
mirror being held up to them. And I
don't want to make you reluctant to say
we don't you're from Venezuela. Not that
I could. Of course I could.
>> There's no way you're going to get stop
[__]
>> right. I take no responsibility for
that. Um but there are certain phrases I
think uh but I think um yeah I think you
are definitely the harder one to to
crack. I think
>> I find it interesting that people react
badly to them because to me number one
it's a sign that you've kind of made it
when people are doing impersonations of
you and people recognize the
impersonation
>> and two it's it's a compliment that
people take the time like impressionists
take the time in order to create what
they think is an impression of you.
Yeah, I agree. Um I think I think I
remember the very first one I did of
James O'Brien many years ago at the
height of Brexit. Uh he gave me a few
shoutouts. He he actually it's on there
somewhere on YouTube somewhere of him
saying I was Mike Yarwood level. I was
very proud of that kind of thing. And I
I I just think that the the problem when
you do political impressions and I do
now, but but it was the war that got me
into political impressions. The war, the
Israel Hamas war. Before that, I just
had a whole bank of them. I never did
them. I just did sports ones. They got
into this to do basically boxing and and
TV shows. But with political
impressions, sometimes people will see
them the the victim, the target, and
they'll probably think this is a
reflection of his opinions. And the
truth is it isn't always. The truth is
sometimes it is. And sometimes it's just
a pinch of both. Um, and so sometimes,
you know, they'll take something that
I've said. And I could do an impression
of Russell Brand and very easily he
could hear what I'm saying, think I'm
making fun of him or finding him guilty
or not. I could do Andrew Tate and
they'll think, "Oh, this reflects how he
feels about me." Any of them.
>> Um but it isn't always. So some of them
don't always like it.
>> He's actually a massive Andrew Tay and
Russell Brown fan.
>> Who Who is me? Yeah. I'm actually a
massive fan of them. Yeah. Yeah.
>> Yeah.
>> Um I was going to say you've got to do
before we go, you've got to do Have you
seen this Tyson Fury?
>> No. It's amazing.
>> Why? I don't understand why we didn't
ask him to do it. Well, because because
this was meant to be political. Yeah.
And what you do is a lot of politics.
And so when you're doing Tyson Fury as
well. Yeah. You got to stick your jaw
out a little bit like that. You know
what I'm talking about? And you've got
to sniff and you've got to breathe in
through your teeth. Yeah. Because so far
no one's knocked my teeth out. So I'm
able to breathe in through them. And
when you're the best heavyweight
champion in the world, what's ever lived
in history, Yeah. you can call yourself
a gypsy king. So when you're the best
Venezuelan what's ever lived in in
heavyweight history, you can call
yourself the king of Venezuela. Maybe
you can actually overtake overthrow and
overtake Maduro. Maybe you can do that.
I don't know. I don't know. We'll see.
>> Can you do a Dana White?
>> He sounds so good in my in my when I do
it to myself. No. Um I can do I can do
some others I've been giving a go.
>> Which ones?
>> Uh but but but not harsh judgment here,
right? These are works in progress. My
my David Starky is um is one that I'm
working but there's an overlap between
him and Doug Mar and you'll see you've
got you've got to admit there is there
is a certain element of revenge in what
you've done but anyway we we won't get
into that.
>> That's very good.
>> Yeah. That's the basis of what others
didn't we didn't we talk
>> um the Lex Freeman one's always a
popular one. Lex Freeman, you know, one
of your peers, podcaster, who always
talks about love and is always talking
about aliens and loves aliens and loves
everybody and only wants to see the
world of peace. Have you ever read
George Orwell's 1984 or Animal Farm?
>> That's that's basically in a nutshell.
>> And is there anyone else? Oh, Hunter
Biden. Okay, let's do it. Um, Hunter
Biden, someone I'm working on at the
moment. He I watched an interview with
him, excuse me, with him and Nick
Fuentes recently.
>> There's some [__] competition.
>> Yeah. Oh, I'm going to do it. Oh, the
Medi Hassan. Let's get to Medan in a
second. Um Nick Fuentes, Norman
Finkelstein. Oh, the list goes on. Um
Nick Fentes when he he's having this
conversation and he and for some reason
Hunter Bowen keeps saying to him, "No,
this is where you lose me, Nick. This is
where you lose me. The whole thing you
said about the cookies, Nick, it was it
was hurtful. You can understand. I don't
think you meant it, Nick." And he did
mean it. you know the things he said he
just keeps saying that to him. It'll be
funny once I stick a a fake podcast
together. Of course I do the mutan
>> which which of you any of you read Zato?
You've never read Zato, have you?
>> I conduct polls in Zato all the time.
I've been talking about this since 2015.
I've been talking about this and I
publish things online and neither of you
are familiar with it. I do. Anyway,
that's a that's a good Hassan one, but
very hard to do because he speaks so
fast, but yeah.
>> Well, Tony, that so great having you on
the really funny great impressions. uh
where can people find your work?
>> Thank you.
>> And uh tell everybody, you know, we'll
make sure to do a YouTube collab so
people can find you.
>> Well, first of all, thank you to both of
you for having me on. Really appreciate
the shot. Really appreciate just hosting
me.
>> Um so Tony Lapidos YouTube. Um my
YouTube page is the one. Um I'm also on
Instagram and on Tik Tok and on uh on X.
My political impressions are mainly on X
and YouTube and it's more sporty on uh
Instagram and Tik Tok, but uh there's
also plenty of that there. So, the more
the merrier. Uh, support, get behind me
now while it's still early. Right,
>> Tony, thanks for coming on. And, uh,
head on over to triggerpod.co.uk. We'll
see some more impressions and answers to
your questions.
>> Dear Mr. Hitchens, after reading every
word you've ever written, I still don't
know your position on drugs. Do you have
any strong opinions on drugs? Wouldn't
you agree that most people would be
happier if they occasionally indulged in
drugs?